Raymond Arceneaux, MBA

Full Stack Software Developer

Email: dev@raymondarceneaux.com

Phone: (615) 480-0202

Technical Experience

BOS Framework

NTC 2019 Tech Start-Up of the Year Winner
Junior Developer/Product Success Intern (May-July 2020)

- Assists in the product support by providing new users guidance during onboarding and implementation stages
- Supports and contribute to the improvement of product documentation
- Test and demos current Hobby Tier product to provide feedback in regard to UI/UX

Nashville Software School

Intensive part-time 12-month full stack software development bootcamp (Aug 2019- Aug 2020)

- Built browser-based single page applications using React
- Created and maintained relational databases using Microsoft SQL Server
- Source code version control with Git and GitHub

Tech Stack

C#, React, Microsoft SQL Server, .Net Core, Dapper, Postman, JSX, JavaScript, jQuery, Firebase, Git, GitHub, Bootstrap 4, HTML, CSS, Sass, Webpack, Npm, Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code

Front-End Capstone

My-dashbook is a single page CRUD application created to allow users the functionality to make an online legacy journal. Built in React/ JavaScript with Google Gmail Authentication using Firebase to allow users a smooth login process. React Router used to render the various pages creating a clear UI/UX experience. The layout and components of all pages where constructed using Bootstrap 4. The app using Facebook Developer SDK allowing users the ability to comment in the app and share these comments on Facebook in real time.



Website: raymondarceneaux.com GitHub: github.com/rarceneaux LinkedIn: LinkedIn/raymondarceneaux

Professional Experience

State of Tennessee

Real Property Agent (January 2017- Present)

- Processes real estate acquisitions, disposals, easements, and lease request on behalf of state agencies
- Facilitate relationships with state approved vendors by requesting bids and awarding bids
- Tracks and maintains all real estate transaction documents in an internal database

MBA Commercial Realty

Principal Broker (Jan 2016- Dec 2016)

- Operated boutique commercial brokerage firm specializing in tenant representation, land sales and retail development
- Met and conducted development presentations to local zoning officials on behalf of clients
- Conducted 10-year cash flow projections using Argus Valuation DCF

UBS

Client Resolution Specialist (Dec 2012- Jan 2016)

- Received inbound service calls from UBS Financial Services branches to assist in opening, maintaining, and terminating investment accounts
- Handled and responded quickly to market and time sensitive inquiries by following escalation protocols
- Tracked call metrics using PeopleSoft (capture call details, problems/solutions, escalation tickets)

Wells Fargo

Business Specialist (Feb 2010- Dec 2012) Personal Banker (Sept 2009- Feb 2010)

- Reached and exceeded pre-set sale goals in loan revenue, deposit growth and investment referrals
- Created and maintained book of business while building relationships with businesses customers increasing cross-selling revenues
- Volunteered time speaking at local colleges and youth organizations on financial literacy and conducting entrepreneurship workshops

Education

Middle Tennessee State University

Master of Business Administration, Finance 2012 Bachelor of Business Administration, Finance 2009